# **ROY MAGNUSSEN**

**Bar Supervisor - Redlibbets Golf Club** 

Liverpool

roymagnussen@hotmail.com

07946115461

Experienced bar worker with over 4 years in the hospitality industry. Knowledge of several cocktail recipes and Rum, Gin, Vodka and Whiskey based beverages including speciality coffees. Experience in ordering stock to desired level, conditioning and maintaining Real Ales, line cleaning and other general cellar management duties. Efficient in preparing drinks for customers while ensuring the utmost quality is kept. Received barista training and experience making a variety of hot drinks.



# WORK EXPERIENCE

### **Bar Supervisor**

Redlibbets Golf Club - Ash

August 2019 to Present

- Responsible for overseeing the bar staff and ensuring that they are carrying out their jobs correctly
- · Ordering Stock
- Line cleaning
- · Opening/Closing of Building
- Cashing up
- Dealing with Customer complaints
- · Serving customers

#### **Bar Staff**

Shepherd Neame - Yalding

August 2018 to August 2019

- Taking customers orders
- · Making drinks
- · Serving drinks and food to customers
- Cleaning tables and resetting them
- · Serving customers

#### **Bar Manager**

The Two Brewers - Hadlow

June 2017 to June 2018

- · Managing Stock
- Line cleaning
- Opening/Closing of Building
- · Conditioned ales
- · Serving customers



### **EDUCATION**

# Full Stack Web Development - Online Course in Full Stack Web Development

The Code Institute

November 2019 to Present

# **BTEC Level 3 Extended Diploma in IT**

**West Kent College - Tonbridge** September 2016 to July 2018

# **BTEC Level 3 Extended Diploma in Games Development**

**Stoke-on-Trent College** - Stoke-on-Trent September 2015 to July 2016

# GCSE or equivalent

**Thomas Alleyne's High School** - Uttoxeter 2012 to July 2014



SKILLS

Inventory, Time Management, POS, Cash Handling, Cashier, MS Office